Detectives,
I'm inviting you to leave.
I'm gonna try to remain calm,
but will you do me a favor
and tell me what is up with you?
My guys are busting their asses
trying to hide Walt's money
from the feds
and you're tossing yours
out a window?
And I have to hear about your little act
of philanthropy on the news?
Did you hit your head
or something?
Why didn't you call me
the second you got arrested?
What did you say
to Schrader?
Nothing. Jesus. Just chill out.
Chill out? No.
No, I don't chill out right now
because things
have gone nuclear.
I imagine Schrader shared
with you his recent discovery.
Okay, well, then you get
my complete lack of chill.
Just use the money
that I gave you.
No, Saul. Saul, I...
Stop... Saul.
Stop talking. I don't care.
Just... Just make it happen.
Work your magic.
And call me when he's out.
Schweikart and Cokely can come
after me with a restraining order...
...or anything else they got,
I'll be ready.